# MICHAŁ FLAK

 $michal@mflak.eu \cdot mflak.eu \cdot linkedin.com/in/mflak \cdot github.com/elo-siema$ 

#### Summary

Software engineer with over 4 years of professional experience. I'm used to being a generalist in a quickly growing startup. Worked independently, in teams, led teams. I know the pitfalls of young projects having experienced them myself and how to avoid them. Looking for new challenges where I can dive deep and engage fully.

My background is mostly in backend API development (.NET, SQL, Node) and DevOps (AWS), but I have dabbled in many things over the years, including frontend, gamedev, mobile and others.

#### EDUCATION

University of Strathclyde

Glasgow, Scotland

BA Product Design and Innovation

Nov 2015 - Jun 2016 (decided to switch to CS)

AGH University of Science and Technology

Kraków, Poland Nov 2017 - Jun 2021 (ongoing, part-time)

BEng Computer Science

Work Experience

Betsold Ltd

Dec 2018 - Present

Remote

 $Lead\ DevOps\ Engineer$ 

- Tasked with setting up CI/CD pipelines and scalable infrastructure in AWS for our product
- Led a team of 4 DevOps and Cloud engineers
- Carried out load tests, identified and strengthened weak points
- Participated in preparations for ISO/IEC 27001 certification
- Managed releases
- Conducted a successful product launch

Betsold Ltd

Glasgow, Scotland / Remote July 2016 - Dec 2018

Software Engineer

- Joined in early stages of a sports betting auction startup, saw its journey to launch
- Developed API in C# / Asp.NET MVC + SQL procedures
- Developed Node.js microservices and AWS lambdas
- Worked on front-end occasionally

Twenty Squares Ltd

Remote

Project Manager / Software Engineer

July 2018 - October 2018

- Worked with a Junior Developer on a redesign / overhaul of a climate change educational game for schools
- Built content structure and presentation templates in Umbraco CMS
- Built a 3d game on PlayCanvas engine
- Rolled out to several Scottish primary schools, positive feedback from kids :)

#### SKILLS

#### Tech - Work:

- AWS deep experience. Used: ASGs, ELB, CodeDeploy, CloudFormation, CloudWatch, Elastic Beanstalk, CloudFront, Route 53, Lambda, RDS, Elasticache, setting up VPCs, SQS, monitored and optimized costs
- Languages: C#, SQL (MySQL, MSSQL), Javascript, Powershell, HTML+CSS, Python, GLSL
- Frameworks: Asp. NET MVC/Core, Umbraco, PlayCanvas, Angular
- Tools/libs: GoCD, Prometheus, Artillery, Git, Redis

### Tech - Hobby / Academic:

• Languages: C, C++, Java, Rust, Haskell, Matlab/Octave

## Other:

• Computer Science fundamentals, complexity analysis, performance optimization

## Projects

Chip8 emulator Rust

https://github.com/elo-siema/rust-chip8

Simple game console emulator written in Rust to familiarise myself with the language.

Compers

Machine Learning Coursera by Andrew Ng